MUHAMMAD TARMIZI BIN ZILANI

MECHATRONICS ENGINEER

CONTACT		
-	+601133789524	
\boxtimes	tarmizizilani64@gmail.com	
	https://mizisport.github.io/Portfolio/	
()	867-3 Jalan Mahang, Bukit Kuang, 24000 Kemaman, Terengganu	

EDUCATION

Penang Skills Development Centre, PSDC

Malaysian Skills Advanced Diploma in Mechatronic

01/2021 - 03/2023

Malaysian Skills Certificate level 3 in Mechatronic

07/2019 - 12/2020

Malaysian-German Chamber of Commerce and Industry, MGCC

Certificate German Dual Vocational Training Mechatronic Technician in Malaysia

07/2019 - 01/2023

SKILLS

- PLC programming & troubleshoot (Siemens, Omron)
- Electrical panel box installation, commissioning and troubleshooting
- Robot programming and Integration (TMflow, RoboDK)
- Software implementation. (Python, C/C++, HTML, Arduino)
- Network troubleshooting (Cisco)
- Automated communication system (Profinet, Profibus)
- Mechanical Design (AutoCad)
- Automation system development
- Project management
- Hydraulics and pneumatics (Festo, SMC)
- Sensors and Instrumentation
- Microsoft Office (word, excel, project, powerpoint)



PROFILE

I am an engineering technician with four years of experience in the manufacturing industry. My expertise lies in troubleshooting, problem solving, and ideas. and I have a proven track record of developing projects for improvement in production. In my previous roles at Bbraun. I successfully accomplished the company goal at the technician and apprenticeship level. I am excited about the opportunity to bring my skills and experience to my future team and contribute to future projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Production Technician

BBRAUN Medical Industries SDN. BHD.

03/2023 - present

- Perform troubleshooting and resolve technical problems in the product line or process to minimize reject levels.
- Servicing and maintenance of machine parts or equipment such as vacuum generators, cylinder grippers, flex conveyors, etc.
- Perform a daily machine check-up to maintain smooth operation.
- Good Documentation Practice (GDP), such as reporting machine condition, tasks, output, downtime, etc.
- Support team members in solving major machine breakdowns and projects.

Mechatronic Apprenticeship

BBRAUN Medical Industries SDN. BHD.

07/2019 - 03/2023

- · Training Industrial Automation Engineering System Assembly
- Develop digital display with webpage as remote to reset counter order by Aesculap Safety department.
- Support production in designing and fabricating part that aid in reducing machine stoppages and projects.
- Training Industrial Automation Engineering System Development
- Develop Vision System Module for Auto-loading and integrate with Computer Vision.
- Involve in designing and fabricating of Disposable Elastomeric Pump Leak Tester order by Plastic Technology Department.
- Involve in programming and circuit design for developing Arduino keyboard module that able the Zwick tester and COBOT to communicate.
- Coaching on how to troubleshoot electrical panel box and PLC programming.

Assistant Technician

12/2018 - 06/2019

Iznor Electrical Engineering

- Troubleshoot Steel Drum Cutter and Curler Machine electrical panel.
- Troubleshoot general electrical appliances.
- Repair water pump and vacuum pump.
- Preventative maintenance air compressor.
- Office work such as quotation, invoice, etc.

REFERENCES

BBraun Medical Industries SDN. BHD.	Iznor Electrical Engineering
+6046323100	+601116815523
www.bbraun.com.my	iznoree@gmail.com